in all honesty on the subject of rebor
en honor a la verdad en el tema de rebor
or rather what Juan knows or Juan would know about
o sea lo que sabe Juan o sabría Juan de
rebor I honestly don't know if it
rebor Yo es que sinceramente no sé si
leaves rebor as bad as the rest of those
deja tan mal a rebor como al recho de
involved I have kept quiet for a long
implicados me he callado durante mucho
time out of respect now I won't keep quiet
tiempo por respeto ahora ya no me callo
a [ __ ] [ __ ] what the [ __ ] is Juan
una [__] [__] de qué [__] va Juan
garnizo about The cuckold the cuckold this
garnizo El cornamentas el cornudo este
shitty guy giving lessons on Twitter
de [__] dando lecciones en Twitter
after all the [ __ ] you've
después de todas las [__] que has
done after all you've done you
hecho después de todo lo que has hecho
still have enough to give him
todavía tienes lo justo para tú darle de
something it's that they've told me
algo es que me han contado cosas
horrible things tell them now well watch out
horribles cuéntalas ahora bien ojito
Because I do have proof Kingman you
Porque yo sí tengo pruebas Kingman tú
are a shitty fan Boy of the
eres un fan Boy de [__] de los
streamers who do whatever the [ __ ] you want to you, I
streamers que os hacen lo que os da la
mean literally idolize
[__] gana o sea literalmente idolatres
scum Juan a [ __ ] Beta by the book
gentuza Juan un [__] Beta de manual
tomorrow rebor will be Banned from Twitch Yes
mañana rebor estará Ban de Twitch Sí es
what he's doing is
baneable lo que está haciendo
obviously bannable yes yes yes yes man Of course
evidentemente sí sí sí sí hombre Claro
apart from that Juan is going to report him you
aparte es que Juan lo va a reportar ya
know that Juan reports cuckold with
sabéis que Juan reporta cornudo con
sense cuckold with sense giving
sentido cornudo cons sentido dando
lessons that I live in fear
leciones de que que yo vivo con miedo